{
  "student": [
    {
      "username": "test",
      "email": "test@gmail.com",
      "password": "123",
      "roles": [
        "STUDENT"
      ],
      "subjects": [
        {
          "id": "d046",
          "name": "AYMAN TISSIR",
          "degree": 16,
          "totalSubject": 16
        },
        {
          "id": "4",
          "name": "subject 4",
          "degree": 1,
          "totalSubject": 3
        },
        {
          "id": "3",
          "name": "subject 3",
          "degree": 0,
          "totalSubject": 3
        },
        {
          "id": "eab5",
          "name": "maths",
          "degree": 0,
          "totalSubject": 5
        },
        {
          "id": "ba76",
          "name": "tdgrsfea",
          "degree": 0,
          "totalSubject": 8
        },
        {
          "id": "7247",
          "name": "arabic",
          "degree": 8,
          "totalSubject": 10
        }
      ],
      "id": "1"
    },
    {
      "username": "Aziz",
      "email": "Aziz@gmail.com",
      "password": "BO9AL2023",
      "roles": [
        "STUDENT"
      ],
      "id": "2"
    },
    {
      "username": "ahmed",
      "email": "ahmed@gmail.com",
      "password": "123",
      "roles": [
        "STUDENT"
      ],
      "subjects": [
        {
          "id": "d046",
          "name": "AYMAN TISSIR",
          "degree": 16,
          "totalSubject": 16
        }
      ],
      "id": "3"
    },
    {
      "username": "Hassan",
      "email": "HASSAN@gmail.com",
      "password": "SOSO2023",
      "roles": [
        "STUDENT"
      ],
      "id": "4"
    }
  ],
  "admin": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "email": "admin@gmail.com",
      "password": "123",
      "roles": [
        "ADMIN"
      ],
      "id": "1"
    }
  ],
  "professor": [
    {
      "username": "Aziz",
      "email": "prof@gmail.com",
      "password": "123",
      "roles": [
        "PROFESSEUR"
      ],
      "id": "1"
    }
  ],
  "subjects": [
    {
      "id": "3",
      "name": "subject 3",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "j",
          "answer1": "j",
          "answer2": "j",
          "answer3": "j",
          "answer4": "j",
          "correctAnswer": "mm",
          "note": 3
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "name": "subject 4",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "1",
          "answer1": "a",
          "answer2": "s",
          "answer3": "d",
          "answer4": "f",
          "correctAnswer": "a",
          "note": 1
        },
        {
          "question": "2",
          "answer1": "a",
          "answer2": "s",
          "answer3": "d",
          "answer4": "f",
          "correctAnswer": "b",
          "note": 2
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "d046",
      "name": "AYMAN TISSIR",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "10*2",
          "answer1": "20",
          "answer2": "2",
          "answer3": "10",
          "answer4": "11",
          "correctAnswer": "20",
          "note": 3
        },
        {
          "question": "10+5",
          "answer1": "3",
          "answer2": "15",
          "answer3": "2",
          "answer4": "12",
          "correctAnswer": "15",
          "note": 7
        },
        {
          "question": ",11+11",
          "answer1": "11",
          "answer2": "30",
          "answer3": "22",
          "answer4": "0",
          "correctAnswer": "22",
          "note": 6
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "maths",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "premiere question",
          "answer1": "answe1",
          "answer2": "answer2",
          "answer3": "answer3",
          "answer4": "answer4",
          "correctAnswer": "answe1",
          "note": 5
        }
      ],
      "id": "eab5"
    },
    {
      "id": "ba76",
      "name": "tdgrsfea",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "jyhtgrfseadw",
          "answer1": "hgg",
          "answer2": "hngbdfd",
          "answer3": "gnbfvd",
          "answer4": "ngbfv",
          "note": 8,
          "correctAnswer": "ngbfv"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "7247",
      "name": "arabic",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "2*2",
          "answer1": "3",
          "answer2": "4",
          "answer3": "1",
          "answer4": "5",
          "note": 2,
          "correctAnswer": "4"
        },
        {
          "question": "5+5",
          "answer1": "10",
          "answer2": "1",
          "answer3": "100",
          "answer4": "0",
          "note": 2,
          "correctAnswer": "10"
        },
        {
          "question": "racine carre de 4",
          "answer1": "1",
          "answer2": "3",
          "answer3": "2",
          "answer4": "10",
          "note": 2,
          "correctAnswer": "2"
        },
        {
          "question": "le carre de 3",
          "answer1": "3",
          "answer2": "4",
          "answer3": "2",
          "answer4": "9",
          "note": 2,
          "correctAnswer": "9"
        },
        {
          "question": "1*0",
          "answer1": "5",
          "answer2": "4",
          "answer3": "2",
          "answer4": "0",
          "note": 2,
          "correctAnswer": "0"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}